plexfund.com 2011-05-15

# Plex Fund Online Investment Program

**What is this policy about?**

Plex Fund Investments recognizes the importance of ensuring that our customers have confidence in the way we handle personal information.

 **What is personal information?**

Personal information is any information about an individual that identifies the individual or by which their identity can reasonably be ascertained.

 **What kinds of personal information do we collect and hold about you?**

Plex Fund only collects personal information that is necessary for one or more of our functions or activities. The types of personal information which are collected from our clients and suppliers (including employees of our clients or suppliers) includes name, address and other contact details, as well as information about products and services which those individuals request from Plex Fund.

 **How is personal information collected?**

Most information we hold about clients is collected over the phone or via the Internet during the course of the client?s relationship with Plex Fund. Sometimes, information about an individual is collected from other people or organizations. For example, information about a director of a corporate client may be obtained from a public record relating to the company. Regardless of how it is collected, all personal information is handled in accordance with this privacy policy.

 **What does Plex Fund Investments use your personal information for?**

Plex Fund uses the personal information we hold in order to provide our clients with the services they request. These services are funds management and related services. Providing a client with service includes undertaking activities such as providing client support, responding to enquiries and requests for product information and providing funds management.

If Plex Fund is unable to collect personal information from or about an individual, we may be unable to do business with that individual or the organization with which the individual is connected. We may also use personal information for our own internal purposes and we may use that information for marketing purposes, to inform you about new products and services or special offers from time to time. If you do not wish to receive marketing material from Plex Fund, please let us know by contacting us and we will cease sending it to you.

Plex Fund Investments may also collect personal information from its suppliers in order to complete business transactions and purchase products and services.

If we want to use your information for purposes other than those set out above, we will request your consent.

 **Does Plex Fund disclose the personal information it holds?**

Sometimes Plex Fund obtains services from other organizations and where necessary (and where the law permits), personal information will be provided to those organizations. The kinds of services obtained externally by Plex Fund include information technology support, financial advice, legal advice and the use of settlement and clearing systems.

External service providers are only authorised to use personal information for the purpose for which Plex Fund supplied it. Those organizations are not authorised to use that information for their own purposes.

Where a customer nominates someone to act on their behalf, Plex Fund may provide information to that person, for example, the client?s accountant or financial adviser.

Security and accuracy of personal information

Plex Fund will take reasonable steps to ensure that all personal information we collect or use is:

\- Accurate, complete and up-to-date

\- Stored in a secure environment

-  Accessed only by authorized personnel for permitted purposes

If your details change, we ask that you advise us of the change as soon as possible in order that we may maintain accurate records.

 **Website**

We have implemented procedures and installed equipment to safeguard the security and confidentiality of personal information collected via our website. We continually review these arrangements to ensure that we are doing all that is reasonably a technically feasible at the time to protect your information, although because of the nature of the internet, we cannot guarantee that it is totally protected from hackers or misuse.

This privacy policy does not apply if you access another website through a link from ours. In this case the privacy policy (if any) of the owner of the other website, will apply. We cannot and do not make any warranty or representation as to the practices of any linked websites in the handling of your personal information.

 **Resolving concerns**

If you believe that the privacy of your personal information has been compromised, you are entitled to complain. Complaints can be made by contacting us using Contact Us form. We will respond to your concerns as soon as possible.
